CASSANDRA KEDDIS FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

\$ 858-306-2758

Vancouver, BC

in cassandra-keddis

n cassie-eve

EDUCATION

SUMMARY

Applied Web Development program

2020 to Current

Lighthouse Labs

Sept. 2022 to Apr. 2023

Full-stack web developer who went from Culinary school and kitchens to a career in technology that started in 2017. I strive to be highly efficient with a goal to learn something new and better myself every day, and my experience in customer facing roles has given me a strong understanding of customer sentiment and helps me to build highly intuitive products. I am a strong communicator that looks forward to working in fast paced and ever changing environments.

Mar 2022 to Current

Feb. 2017 to Aug. 2020

SKILLS

Languages: Javascript, Ruby, HTML, CSS FRAMEWORKS & LIBRARIES: NodeJS, React, Ajax, Express, EJS, jQuery, Rails SYSTEMS & DATABASES: PostgreSQL, Git TESTING: Jest, Storybook ,Cypress, RSpec, Mocha, Chai

EMPLOYMENT

THINKIFIC, VANCOUVER BC

Verify and find reproduction steps for issues reported by our Technical Team to save time for our Product team and resolve issues faster

Work alongside our Engineering team to identify and resolve bugs across the application taking work off our Engineering team's plate Improve documentation and processes for the Technical and Escalation teams ensuring consistency and faster onboarding

Coach and up-level members of the Technical Team allowing for better quality escalations and fewer requests for additional investigation

Manage internal requests within the Success department that require an understanding of our codebase resulting in much faster internal support and taking away less resources from Engineering

Actively taking more than 80% of database updates from Engineering's backlog which means faster resolutions for our customers

Responsible for many internal applications, integrations, and tools that help our department to run effectively applications.

Technical Escalations Team Lead

Feb. 2021 to Mar. 2022 Streamlined our team's processes and implemented Key Performance Indicators so team members had a better understanding of what they needed to improve

Improved and implemented a new company-wide incident response process allowing for much faster recognition of emergencies and faster time to a resolution

Managed a team of 6 ensuring the prioritization of their professional development helping team members to progress in their careers Worked with other departments on projects across the company to streamline processes and ensure better cross-team collaboration

Senior Technical Escalations Specialist

Aug. 2020 to Feb. 2021

Acted as the liaison between customer-facing teams and our Engineering department, which improved communication and expedited issue resolution. Served as the on-call Communication lead during company-wide incidents, ensuring clear and effective communication in high-stress situations to facilitate quick resolutions

Identified and wrote technical documentation for bugs, providing our Engineering team with clear and actionable reports to resolve issues faster
Assisted customers with more technical issues, ensuring their success and satisfaction, which led to higher customer retention and positive feedback

 $Supported \ developers \ integrating \ their \ products \ with \ our \ API, \ helping \ to \ expand \ our \ platform's \ capabilities \ and \ reach$

Communicated with escalated customers with technical questions, ensuring they received accurate and timely information to maintain trust

CLIO, BURNABY BC

Coached members of our Customer Support team through more technical questions, enhancing their ability to support our customers effectively

Worked directly with customers to troubleshoot complex issues escalated to our team, reducing resolution times and increasing customer satisfaction
Provided support for our API and assisted developers wanting to integrate with our platform, fostering stronger developer relationships and expanding our ecosystem

Identified and documented issues to forward to our Development teams, ensuring that problems were clearly communicated and quickly addressed

PROJECTS

Listify is a smart to-do list application that uses a machine learning API to automatically classify tasks.

Tech stack: Express, SCSS, EJS, and Node.js

TINYAPP

RESTful URL Shortening service built with Node and Express.

Tech stack: Node.js, Express, Javascript, HTML, CSS

React based project to create meetings for students to connect with mentors in real-time.

Tech stack: React, Axios, Classnames, Normalize, Storybook

AWARDS

THINKIFIC 2024 CHOICE AWARDS

Representing my commitment to our company values.

CLIQ 2020 IMPACT AWARDS

Representing my commitment to our company values.

VOLUNTEERING

Current